

# **MATEO LIBERATORE**

STUDENT OF THE HIGHER TECHNICAL CAREER IN SYSTEMS ANALYSIS



+54 223 4556948



liberatoremate98@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/mateo-liberatore



https://github.com/MateoLiberatore

I am a proactive, organized, and responsible person with excellent interpersonal skills. I have 6 months of real experience developing in a production environment and am currently working on personal projects in areas of my interest. I am also in the process of completing my last courses for the Higher Technical Degree in Systems Analysis.

## **EDUCATION**

#### ISFT N° 151

2021- TODAY

Higher Technical Degree in Systems Analysis

### **Programatic Accenture &** Conciencia

2023

Data Science and Soft Skills Training Data analysis, processing, and collection with Python libraries

### **SKILLS**

- Windows Linux / Ubuntu
- git / GitHub GitLab JavaScript / React Node
- HTML / CSS
- Python / Flask / Apache-Airflow
- SQL / Postgres MySQL SQLite / SQLAlchemy
- Advanced English (reading, writing, and conversational)

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Buonaterra, June 2024 - December 2024

Development and maintenance of healthcare applications, user management, web development, documentation, and record-keeping.

#### **Administrative Assistant**

Orcamein SA, June 2022 - May 2024

Invoicing, stock control, management and preparation of wholesale orders, management of retail order deliveries, PC maintenance, use and maintenance of management software.

## **PROYECTS**

### **Pixel Mech Mayhem**

Prototipado de videojuego 2D, hecho en JavaScript vanilla usando MVC, manejo de estados y eventos. Esta es una version de muestra utilizada para una muestra promocional de la carrera.



https://github.com/MateoLiberatore/Pixel-Mech-Mayhem



https://mateoliberatore.github.io/Pixel-Mech-Mayhem